Dolores Miller ILGWU Photographs 6036/091 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Dolores Miller ILGWU Photographs
1971-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Miller, Dolores
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
6036/091 P
1.61 cubic feet
1.6 linear ft.
Photographs.
8595061
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6036/091 AV: Dolores Miller ILGWU Audio-Visual Materials 6036/091 MB: Dolores Miller ILGWU Memorabilia 6036/091 PUBS: Dolores Miller ILGWU and Other Publications
Miller, Dolores; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
8595061
- ILGWU School for Workers - photo album contents (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Conference and Parade Photos (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Zelma Young - Photo autographed by Hubert Humphrey (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rose Day (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mary Louise - Letters - Harold Schwartz (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Conferences, Workshops, Misc. Group Photos (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous loose photos (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous loose photos (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous loose photos (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Unmarked/labeled photo album (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Unmarked/unlabeled photo album (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Convention photos & miscellaneous loose photos (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous photos (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Convention (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mondale 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Rosie Day Retirement Lobby, Springfield, Ill. - May 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Unity House - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Photos & Negs. (Unity House) - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Unity House - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Photos & Negs (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 9)
- June 1981 - School of Workers (Box 2, Folder 10)
- June 1981 - School of Workers (Box 2, Folder 11)
- CLUW Conference (Box 2, Folder 12)
- CLUW Conference (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1981 - State Fair & Unity House (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Photos, Membership Cards (2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Convention (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Photos & Negs (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Photos & Negs. (Box 2, Folder 30)
- & Negs. (Box 2, Folder 31)
- 1992 Convention (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 1992 Convention (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Trip to New York City (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Trip to New York City (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Trip to New York City (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Dolores Miller (Box 3, Folder 35)
- 34th Convention - International Ladies Garment Workers Union AFL-CIO, Miami Beach, Florida - May 6-14, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  panoramic photo
- 35th Convention International ladies Garment Workers Union, AFL-CIO - Miami Beach, Florida -- May 31-June 7, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)